<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="rent_repair_report_tag" model="ir.actions.report">
            <field name="name">Repair Policy</field>
            <field name="model">property.rent</field>
            <field name="report_type">qweb-pdf</field>
            <field name="report_name">property_lease_management.repair_policy_template</field>
            <field name="report_file">property_lease_management.repair_policy_template</field>
            <field name="print_report_name">'Repair Policy-%s' %(time.strftime('%d-%m-%Y'))</field>
            <field name="paperformat_id" ref="property_lease_management.paperformat_policies"/>
            <field name="binding_model_id" ref="model_property_rent"/>
            <field name="binding_type">report</field>
        </record>

        <template id="repair_policy_template">
            <t t-call="web.html_container">
                <div class="page">
                    <img t-if="docs[0].company_id.report_image1"
                         t-att-src="image_data_uri(docs[0].company_id.report_image1)"
                         style="max-height: 110px;width:150px" alt="Logo"/>
                    <div class="row">
                        <center>
                            <h1>
                                <strong><u>NOTICE</u>
                                    <br/>
                                </strong>
                            </h1>
                            <span style="color:black;border-bottom:1px solid !important;">
                                For ordinary repair &amp; maintenance, visit will be every
                                <strong>SATURDAY</strong> only.
                            </span>
                            <br/>
                            <br/>
                        </center>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="row" style="">
                    <div style="text-align:justify;font-size:14px;!important;">
                        <strong>REPAIRS POLICY &amp; PROCEDURE</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        In the event that you require repairs and maintenance to be carried out at the property you must
                        first contact Aqar Real Estate (via the maintenance-in-charge) Mr Duraid
                        <span style="color:blue;">duraid.aqar@gmail.com</span>
                        and report what the problem is. Once we have discussed the matter with the Landlord we will
                        arrange for the relevant personnel to carry out the required work which tenant should allow us
                        to do so inside the flat. If you seek the services of a third party without notifying and
                        approval from Aqar Real Estate, you will be liable for the cost of the repair.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>ONLY</strong>
                        calls and report from the
                        <strong>TENANT REGISTRED</strong> in the Tenancy Agreement will be entertained.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>TAKE CARE OF YOUR PROPERTY</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        You need to look after the property and avoid causing any damage. Your responsibilities as a
                        tenant include:
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        • &#160;&#160;Cleanliness – your home must be kept clean-fair wear and tear is accepted, damage is not
                        <br/>
                        • &#160;&#160;Carrying out basic maintenance – for example checking alarms work, changing light bulbs etc.
                        <br/>
                        • &#160;&#160;Tenants are not authorized to carry forward any work from outside and in order to proceed the
                        work from in house the gate pass must require from
                        <strong>AQAR REAL ESTATE.</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        If you cause any damage to the property or the furniture, fixtures and fittings in the property,
                        either accidentally or on purpose, your Landlord is entitled to make you pay for the damage. In
                        some cases, your Landlord may ask you to carry out the repairs yourself if it is deemed as your
                        responsibility.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>OUT-OF-HOURS AND EMERGENCY CALL-OUTS</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        Aqar Real Estate is open <strong>Sunday to Thursday from 8:00am – 6:00pm.</strong> You can
                        contact the
                        maintenance-in-charge at any time during these hours to report a repair.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        If the problem is <strong>not an emergency</strong> you must wait and contact Aqar Real Estate
                        <strong>during office hours.
                            <u>An Emergency is classed as a situation which is sudden and dangerous, an impending
                                situation that may cause injury, loss of life or severe damage to the property.
                            </u>
                        </strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        Thank you.
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>The Management</strong>
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        <strong>Maintenance-in-Charge:</strong> (79434430), you may also contact Caretaker of the respected building for
                        the same.
                        <br/>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>
